A Guide to the Louis Arthur Johnson Papers, ca. 1930-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series V. Papers of the Secretary of Defense
  - Subseries A, General Correspondence
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Louis Johnson's visit to Yeshiva University for Dedication Exercises 1949 May-June (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: 35th Division Reunion 1949 Jan. 24-Aug. (Box 128)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Neal Dow Becker Publisher's Dinner 1949 March 3-May (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: Conference of National Organizations 1949 March 4-April (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: National Celebrities Golf Tournament 1949 March 8-May (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: West Virginia, Department of Veterans Affairs Council Meeting 1949 March 9-July (Box 128)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: 1949 National Convention of the American Red Cross 1949 March 9-July (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: Women's National Press Club Annual Dinner 1949 March 15-May (Box 128)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: U. S. S. ROANOKE commissioning 1949 March 16-May (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: an address at the Annual Meeting of the Association of Casualty and Surety Cos. 1949 March 17-1950 June (Box 128)
    - Correspondence with Lawrence Spivak re: "Meet the Press" 1949 March 21-1950 Aug. (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: Business Advisory Council 1949 March 22-April (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: American Legion State Convention, West Virginia 1949 March 28-July (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: International Association of Insurance Council 1949 March 29-April (Box 128)
    - Correspondence re: Burning Tree, Golf Tournament 1949 March 30-April (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Commemoration of Sherman's War is Hell!" speech 1949 March 30-July (Box 129)
    - Invitation, French Ambassador 1949 March 30-April 2 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Navy Ball 1949 March 30-April (Box 129)
    - Invitation, U. S. Joint Chiefs of Staff 1949 March 31 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, the Commandant, USMC 1949 April 1 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, His Britannic Majesty's Ambassador 1949 April 2 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Italian Ambassador 1949 April 2 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Eugene Myers 1949 April 4 (Box 129)
    - Invitation to signing ceremony, North Atlantic Treaty 1949 April 4 (Box 129)
    - Memo re: T. W. Hacker 1949 April 5 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: National Board of Fire Underwriters Dinner 1949 April 5-June (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: American Society of Newspaper Editors Banquet 1949 April 7-May (Box 129)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: the "military mind" before the Society for Newspaper Editors 1949 April 7-22 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of the Philippines 1949 April 8 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: California Manufacturers Association Annual Banquet 1949 April 9-July (Box 129)
    - Invitation from Albert Cox 1949 April 11 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Independence Day address, Boston 1949 April 11, 18 (Box 129)
    - Address by Louis Johnson at the Second Joint Orientation Course, Fort Benning, Georgia 1949 April 11 (Box 129)
    - Memo - National Press Club Speech 1949 April 12 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: "I Am An American Day" address, N. Y. 1949 April 12-20 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Luncheon invitation from Harry F. Byrd 1949 April 12-1950 June (Box 129)
    - Invitation, the Colombian Ambassador 1949 April 13, 19 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Secretary of State 1949 April 13 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, the Chatterbox Club 1949 April 14 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Copies of various speeches made by Secretary of Defense Johnson 1949 April 15-1950 June (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Recognition dinner in Clarksburg 1949 April 18-June (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Capital Airlines 1949 April 18, 22 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: "Salute to President of Israel" 1949 April 19-21 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence re: Ceremonies on V-J Day 1949 April 19-May (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Rear Admiral F. Stam 1949 April 21 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence with Samuel F. Haines, M. D., Mayo Clinic 1949 April 22-29 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Joseph Davies 1949 April 24 (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Hoosier reception 1949 April 24 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Johnson's visit to Ottawa, 11 August 1949 1949 April 25-Aug. (Box 129)
    - Invitation, Sir Frederick Shedden 1949 April 27 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, the Congressional Club 1950 April 27 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Secretary of Commerce 1951 April 27 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: a speech at the Air War College 1949 April 28-1950 March (Box 130)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Congress of American Industry Address 1949 April 29-Dec. (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Mrs. George Mesta 1949 April 30 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Mr. Justice Reed 1949 May 1 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: American Forestry Association Meeting 1949 May 4-Aug. (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: the Chatterbox Club 1949 May 4-June (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: Time, Inc. 1949 May 4-12 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Chief of Staff, U. S. Army 1949 May 4 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: National War College graduation exercises 1949 May 5-June (Box 130)
    - Memo re: Gridiron Dinner 1949 May 5-June (Box 130)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's remarks before the 37th Annual Meeting of the Chamber of Commerce 1949 May-June 9 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: talks before the Roanoke Chamber of Commerce 1949 May 6-1950 Feb. (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: Kiwanis International Convention 1949 May 11-July (Box 130)
    - Memo re: Veterans Administration Radio Show 1949 May 12 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: Highway Safety Conference 1949 May 12-June (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: 80th birthday of M. L. Benedum 1949 May 12-July (Box 130)
    - Invitation, the Vice-President 1949 May 13 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: Maryland State Bar Association Address 1949 May 13 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Reception for Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt 1949 May 14 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Industrial College of the Armed Forces 1949 May 17, 20 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: Cheyenne Frontier Days Rodeo 1949 May 17, 23 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, John Osborne, Time, Inc. 1949 May 18, 21 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, President Truman 1949 May 18 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence with J. Raymond Berry, National Board of Fire Underwriters 1949 May 19 (Box 130)
    - Invitations, President of Brazil 1949 May 20, 21 (Box 130)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Argentina 1949 May 25 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence re: L. Johnson's speech re: a memorial tablet to Thomas Jefferson 1949 May 25-Sept. (Box 130)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: an international "building code" for world peace before the National Board of Fire Underwriters 1949 May 26-Oct. (Box 131)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: The American Legion Convention in Philadelphia 1949 May 27-Sept. (Box 131)
    - Correspondence re: Blair Moody Dinner 1949 May 31-June (Box 131)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech at Creighton University 1949 June 2-Aug. (Box 131)
    - Correspondence re: Business Advisory Council Dinner 1949 June 2 (Box 131)
    - Memo re: Perry Brown, American Legion 1949 June 2 (Box 131)
    - Memoranda re: American Legion, Nebraska State Convention 1949 June 8-28 (Box 131)
    - Correspondence re: Bicentennial of Washington and Lee 1949 June 8-July (Box 131)
    - Correspondence re: Ninetieth Division Association Reunion 1949 June 9-Oct. (Box 131)
    - Invitation, British Ambassador 1949 June 9 (Box 131)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech at the Dedication Exercises, Yeshiva University 1949 June-Sept. (Box 131)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Founder's Day Speech, University of Virginia 1949 June 15-1950 April (Box 131)
    - Correspondence re: Louis Johnson's article "Teamwork for Defense," published in the American Magazine, 1949 July 1949 June 15-Aug. (Box 131)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: Defense Dept. policy and plans before the National War College 1949 June 21-Aug. 15 (Box 131)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech on the Red Cross 1949 June 21-Aug (Box 132)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's Fourth of July Speech 1949 June 23-Aug. (Box 132)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Thailand 1949 June 24 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Frederick Alger Post #86, American Legion 1949 June 24-Sept. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Joint Chiefs Meeting 1949 June 30-July (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Munitions Board luncheon 1949 July 1-26 (Box 132)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Pakistan 1949 July 1 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Theater Owners of America dinner 1949 July 5-Sept. (Box 132)
    - Invitation, Women's Nation Press Club 1949 July 6-8 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Moose State 1949 July 11-Aug. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence with Henry L. Stevens, Judge 1949 July 12, 15 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Air Force Association, Navy League, Army Club joint meeting 1949 July 14-Aug. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: the AAA annual meeting 1949 July 15-Nov. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: West Virginia ?Society Dinner 1949 July 19-1950 Feb. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Charles Town V-J Celebration 1949 July 21-Aug. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's Defense Broadcasts, "The Nation's Defenses" 1949 July 22-Oct. (Box 132)
    - Invitation, the Polish Ambassador 1949 July 22 (Box 132)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Burma 1949 July 25, Aug. 18 (Box 132)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Liberia 1949 July 26 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: a speech by J. Wm. Fulbright, "America At the Cross Roads" 1949 July 27-29 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence with Aviator's Post 1949 Aug. 2, 8 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Industrial College of the Armed Forces 1949 Aug. 3-Sept. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: United Nations Week, Detroit 1949 Aug. 5-17 (Box 132)
    - Invitation, American Newspaper Women's Club 1949 Aug. 7 (Box 132)
    - Invitation, the President 1949 Aug. 8 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Annual Inspection of the NACA Flight Propulsion Laboratory, Cleveland 1949 Aug. 9-Sept. (Box 132)
    - Invitation, the Philippine Ambassador 1949 Aug. 9 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Dinner for Pandit Nehru 1949 Aug. 18-Oct. (Box 132)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Union of South Africa 1949 Aug. 19 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: New England Council Annual Meeting 1949 Aug. 19-Nov. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: Freedom House Dinner 1949 Aug. 26-Oct. (Box 132)
    - Correspondence re: American Memorial Foundation Benefit 1949 Sept. 5-9 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: a reception for the President of the Federation Aeronautique Internationale 1949 Sept. 8-14 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: the Army and Navy football game 1949 Sept. 9-Nov. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Navy-Princeton game 1949 Sept. 9, 22 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence with Robert Johnson, Chairman, Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report 1949 Sept. 9-Nov. (Box 133)
    - Invitation, Secretary of the Treasury 1949 Sept. 14 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Gold Medal Award of the Interfaith in Action 1949 Sept. 15-Dec. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: American Federation of Labor Convention 1949 Sept. 15-1950 March (Box 133)
    - Invitations, Secretary of Sate 1949 Sept. 17-Oct. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: World Town Hall Seminar 1949 Sept. 19-Oct. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: L. Johnson's speech re: National defense at the Theatre Owners of America Convention 1949 Sept. 21-29 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: Defense before the American Ordnance Association 1949 Sept. 22-Nov. 9 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Fort Worth Independent Petroleum Association 1949 Sept. 23 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities Convention 1949 Sept. 28-Oct. (Box 133)
    - Invitation, Commandant Potomac River Naval Command 1949 Sept. 29 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Commercial Club of Chicago and Irish Fellowship Club of Chicago speeches 1949 Sept. 29-1950 April (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Athenaeum of Summit, N. J. 1949 Oct. 2, 5 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Fifteenth Air Force Society 1949 Oct. 3-28 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Canadian Women's Clubs luncheon 1949 Oct. 4-Nov. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: the Tax Foundation 1950 Oct. 4-Nov. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: National Executive Committee, American Legion 1951 Oct. 4-Nov. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: a hunting trip with Brooke Claxton, Minister of National Defense 1949 Oct. 4-25 (Box 133)
    - Invitation, British Ambassador 1949 Oct. 6 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence re: Navy-Notre Dame football game 1949 Oct. 7, 14 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: New York Herald Tribune Forum 1949 Oct. 10-Nov. (Box 133)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: reduction of defense expenditures 1949 Oct. 10-1950 March 10 (Box 133)
    - Invitation, the President 1949 Oct. 11 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Washington Chapter of the University of Virginia Alumni Association 1949 Oct. 11-1950 Feb. (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Luncheon with Senators Johnson and Brewster 1949 Oct. 13-14 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: The Sojourners Club 1949 Oct. 13-Nov. (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: United Nations Childrens Fund 1949 Oct. 18 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Kiwanis luncheon 1949 Oct. 19, 24 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Business Advisory Council Luncheon for Nehru at Homestead Hotel 1949 Oct. 19-Nov. (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: The Citizens Army of the U. S. meeting 1949 Oct. 19-21 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Homecoming celebration, West Virginia University 1949 Oct. 21 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Gridiron Dinner 1949 Oct. 24-Dec. (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Eric Johnston 1949 Oct. 24 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: defense policy 1949 Oct. 26-Nov. 25 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Democratic National Committee Dinner 1949 Oct. 27-Dec. (Box 134)
    - Invitation to U. S. Naval Academy 1949 Nov. 1, 3 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Annual Bar Dinner, N. Y. Co. Lawyers' Association 1949 Nov. 4-Dec. (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: preparedness and national defense 1949 Nov. 5-Dec. 16 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Brotherhood Week, 1950 1949 Nov. 6-1950 April (Box 134)
    - Invitation, U. S. S. R. Ambassador 1949 Nov. 7 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Dinner for Harold Stuart 1949 Nov. 9, 14 (Box 134)
    - U. S. Naval Medical School Course description 1949 Nov. 10 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, National Guard 1949 Nov. 10 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Harrison Co. Democratic Club of Women Voters 1949 Nov. 10, 14 (Box 134)
    - Speech by Louis Johnson re: Armistice Day and Defense Economy 1949 Nov. 11 (Box 134)
    - Dinner Invitations from President Truman 1949 Nov. 16-1950 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Post Mortem Club 1949 Nov. 17-23 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Ambassador of Iran 1949 Nov. 18 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech re: National Defense and economy 1949 Nov. 18-Dec. 6 (Box 134)
    - Invitation, Southern Society Meeting 1949 Nov. 22 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence re: Natural Law Institute 1949 Nov. 22-Dec. (Box 134)
    - Invitation, British Ambassador 1949 Nov. 22 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech, "The Ramparts We Watch" 1949 Nov. 23-1950 Jan. 10 (Box 135)
    - Invitation, Commandant Schuirmann 1949 Nov. 26 (Box 135)
    - Invitation, honoring Wm. M. Boyle 1949 Nov. 29, Dec. 2 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: a trip to Paris for the North Atlantic Defense Committee Meetings 1949 Nov.-1950 Jan. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: Dinner in honor of Associate Justice Tom C. Clark 1949 Dec. 1-1950 Jan. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: Over-Seas Writers' Luncheon 1949 Dec. 5-17 (Box 135)
    - Memo re: Presentation of seal of Department of Defense at West Point 1949 Dec. 7 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's speech, "Unification" Means Dollars and Makes Sense" 1949 Dec. 13-1950 Aug. 14 (Box 135)
    - TLS, Mrs. Joseph V. Reed to Louis Johnson 1949 Dec. 16 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: Address at the Command and General Staff College 1949 Dec. 16-1950 Sept. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: the 1950 Kiwanis International Convention 1949 Dec. 23-1950 June (Box 135)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Robert P. Patterson's speech, "Unification in the Armed Forces" 1949 Dec. 29-1950 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: American Ordnance Association Luncheon 1949 Dec. 30-1950 Feb. (Box 135)
    - Draft for March issue of American Legion Magazine, "The First Year is the Hardest" 1949 Dec. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: Jefferson-Jackson Dinner 1950 Jan. 4-Feb. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: Annual Wallow of the Military Order of the Carabao 1950 Jan. 4-Feb. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: the Publisher' Dinner 1950 Jan. 5-1950 May (Box 135)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: a banquet in honor of President Truman 1950 Jan. 6-10 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: An award for Amon Carter 1950 Jan. 9-10 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: A benefit Dog Show 1950 Jan. 9-11 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence re: Norge Ski Club Trophy 1950 Jan. 9-Feb. (Box 135)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Reserve Officers Association Banquet 1950 Jan. 9-July (Box 135)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: John F. Floberg's speech, "Your Navy Today and Tomorrow" 1950 Jan. 13-17 (Box 135)
    - Invitation to dinner in honor of Chiefs of Staff Committee, Canada - U. S. Regional Planning Group, NATO 1950 Jan. 17 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: White House News Photographers' Association Dinner 1950 Jan. 17-Feb. (Box 136)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: the Thirty-fifth Division Reunion at St. Louis 1950 Jan. 18-June (Box 136)
    - Invitation to luncheon for the Vice-President and Mrs. Barkley 1950 Jan. 22 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Annual dinner of the Women's National Press Club 1950 Jan. 25-April (Box 136)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Overseas Press Club of America Annual Dinner 1950 Jan. 25-March (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Breakfast in honor of the President 1950 Jan. 26-Feb. (Box 136)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Depart of Justice Speech 1950 Feb. 6-March (Box 136)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: U. S. Naval Academy speech 1950 Feb. 7-June (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Visit to Key West 1950 Feb. 8-May (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: White House Correspondents' Association Dinner 1950 Feb. 9-March (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Armed Services Liaison Committee 1950 Feb. 13-March (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Reserve Officers Association of Texas Convention 1950 Feb. 13-23 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Exhibition of orchids 1950 Feb. 14-June (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Association of Radio News Analysts Luncheon 1950 Feb. 21-24 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Address at the Industrial College of the Armed Forces, Washington, D. C. 1950 Feb. 21-July (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Eleanor Roosevelt's television debate proposal 1950 Feb. 23-April (Box 136)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: L. Johnson's remarks at the Armed Forces Day Dinner, 20 May 1950 1950 Feb. 23-June (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Union Industries Show 1950 Feb. 28-March (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: A request to speak at Davis-Elkins 1950 March 1-April (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: 14th National School Safety Patrol Parade 1950 March 2-April (Box 136)
    - Correspondence re: Operation Portrex 1950 March 6-15 (Box 136)
    - Miscellaneous dinner and wedding invitations 1950 March 6-Oct. (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: U. S. Savings Bond Dinner 1950 March 7, 13 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Second Division Reunion 1950 March 10-June (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Opening session of the Third Meeting of the North Atlantic Defense Committee 1950 March 11-June (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Dinners by General Bradley 1950 March 12-May (Box 137)
    - Memorandum re: U. S. Air Force Fighter Gunnery Meet 1590 March 14 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: A parade in honor of the Secretary of the Army 1950 March 15-April (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: a telecast "On Trial" 1950 March 22-April (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: a panel discussion on the military budget 1950 April 6-11 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: National Board of Fire Underwriters Dinner 1950 April 6-May (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Joint Exercise SWARMER 1950 April13-15 (Box 137)
    - Address of Lewis L. Strauss before the Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1950 April 14 (Box 137)
    - Invitation to sit on Speakers Stand, Salute to Freedom Celebration 1950 April 14 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Observation of Demon III 1950 April 17-19 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: an exhibition at the Truxton-Decatur Museum 1950 April 20 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Joint Civilian Orientation Conference 1950 April 21-July (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Luncheon on Pier 60 for the initial shipment of food to Berlin 1950 April 21, 24 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Armed Forces Day 1950 April 22-May (Box 137)
    - Invitation to swearing in of Mr. Symington as Chairman of NSRB 1950 April 24 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: the Northwest Institute of International Relations Conference 1950 April 29-June (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: a trip to Ramey Air Forces Base, Puerto Rico 1950 May 4-Aug. (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Speeches by J. Edgar Hoover 1950 May 5-June (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: a speech by General Omar Bradley 1950 May 18, 26 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: the presentation of a trophy by the Army and Navy Journal 1950 May 26, 31 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence re: Monogahela Golf party 1950 May 29-July (Box 137)
    - Lists of invitations regretted by Secretary and Mrs. Johnson 1950 May, July (Box 137)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: a visit to Mexico and other Latin American countries 1950 June 1-Sept. (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: a joint dinner of NSIA and American Ordnance 1950 June 1 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: President's Committee on National Employ-The-Physically-Handicapped Week 1950 June 15-Aug. (Box 138)
    - Invitation to the laying of the Cornerstone, U. S. Courthouse for the District of Columbia 1950 June 27 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Johnson's trip to Japan and visit with the Eighth Army, 2 folders 1950 June (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: West Virginia, Bankers Association Convention 1950 July 17 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: American Federation of Labor Convention 1950 July 19-Sept. (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: the Sesquicentennial of the U. S. Military Academy 1950 July 26-Aug. (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: a cruise on Admiral Sherman's barge 1950 July 31 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: a cruise weekend on board the U. S. S. Sequoia 1950 Aug. 15 (Box 138)
    - Invitation to celebrate the Dominican Republic's Restoration Day 1950 Aug. 16 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: Commanders Banquet, The American Legion Convention 1950 Aug. 26-Sept. (Box 138)
    - Correspondence re: Address at the American Bar Association 1950 Aug. 26-Sept. (Box 138)